Charles Schuchert Archives
Yale Peabody Museum of Natural History
Charles Schuchert Archives
1888-1942
IPAR.001000
Yale Peabody Museum of Natural History
10
The archives consist of field notebooks from 1888-1942, photographs and drawings of both specimens and localities, lists of specimens and localities, miscellaneous material gathered for notes and lectures, and biographical material. There are also hydrographic maps of Newfoundland, and topographic maps of Vermont, Pennsylvania, New York, Texas, and Arizona.
Schuchert, Charles
Biographical Sketch
Charles Schuchert (b. 1856, d. 1942) was born in Cincinnati, Ohio, on July 3, 1856, to Philip and Agatha (Mueller) Schuchert. His father was a woodworker and his parents were in the furniture business. At first, Charles was destined to work in the family business as a bookkeeper, but when he failed to grasp the details of accounting, at the age of 12 he was placed in the varnish room. He spent the next 14 years working for his father or himself, and eventually set up his own business.
Fate intervened for Schuchert when he met Edward O. Ulrich, a fellow Cincinnati native and fossil hunter. For 10 glorious years the 2 were nearly inseparable, collecting local fossils and then later working together in the preparation of paleontological monographs. In 1888, Schuchert moved to Albany, New York, to further his apprenticeship with the ?great professor? James Hall. There, in the company of Hall, John Clarke (New York State Museum) and Charles E. Beecher (Yale University), Schuchert expanded his geological horizons and furthered his knowledge of brachiopods through his collaboration with these 3 workers.
Schuchert was on the move again in 1892, with a brief stop at Yale University for a year, while he worked with Beecher preparing slabs of Crawfordsville crinoids for the ?Chicago Exposition.? From Yale, Schuchert went to the U.S. Geological Survey and U.S. National Museum, where he spent 10 years working with Charles D. Walcott on the invertebrate fossil collections and museum exhibits.
In September 1904 Schuchert was called to Yale University to fill the void vacated by Beecher, who had died earlier that year. At Yale Schuchert?s leadership abilities soon became apparent, and he was appointed to the board of the Sheffield Scientific School (1904?1925), Chair of the Geology Department (1909?1921), and as administrative head of the Yale Peabody Museum (1904?1923). During Schuchert?s tenure he more than doubled the invertebrate fossil collections and trained many of the following generations of eminent paleontologists and stratigraphers.
Description of the Material
Includes Schuchert's personal field notebooks from 1888-1942. Also, maps from his field areas, photographs and drawings of specimens and localities, and miscellaneous other material (both biographic and collections related). Schuchert did extensive field work in the Ordovician rocks of Newfoundland and Quebec (especially Anticosti Island).
Ohio; Connecticut; USA; Correspondence; Field notebooks; Maps; Yale Peabody Museum; Yale University
- Field Notebooks, 1888-1942; Series I
  - Field Notebooks., 1888-1900; 001004
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Ohio., 1888; 000071
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Minnesota, Wisconsin, Iowa, Illinois, Pennsylvania. 1891, 1898, 000072
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Alabama, Mississippi, Wisconsin. 1893, 1896, 000073
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Alabama., 1894; 000074
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Kentucky, Pennsylvania, Tennessee. 1894, 1897, 000075
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Michigan, New York, Ohio, Ontario., 1895; 000076
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Greenland., 1897; 000077
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Greenland., 1897; 000078
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Illinois, Iowa, Kansas, Kentucky, Missouri, New York., 1898; 000079
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Wyoming. 1898, 1899, 000081
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Wyoming., 1899; 000080
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Maryland, New York. 1899, 1900, 1901, 1904, 000082
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: New Brunswick, Quebec, Nova Scotia, Ontario. 1900, 1927, 000083
  - Field Notebooks., 1901-1910; 001005
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: New York, Pennsylvania., 1901; 000084
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Georgia, Virginia, West Virginia., 1902; 000085
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Europe (England, Germany, Denmark, Sweden, Russia, Estland, Estonia, Czechoslovakia, Austria, Belgium; Museum exhibit plans, 1903; 000086
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Europe (England, Germany, Denmark, Sweden, Russia, Estland, Estonia, Czechoslovakia, Austria, Belgium); Museum exhibit plans, 1903; 000087
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Europe (England); (Museum exhibit plans); Missouri (St. Louis Exposition). 1903, 1904, 000088
    - Notebook. Field Notebook and older sections and other C.S. notes: Kentucky, Indiana., 1904; 000089
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: New Brunswick, Nova Scotia, Quebec (Gaspe)., 1905; 000090
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Mexico., 1906; 000091
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: New York, Pennsylvania, Washington, DC. 1906, 1907, 1908, 000092
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Maryland, New Jersey, Tennessee, Virginia, West Virginia, Indiana, Ohio, Ontario, New York., 1907; 000093
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Quebec; Anticosti Is., 1908; 000094
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Maryland, Washington, DC, West Virginia. 1908, 1913, 000107
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Illinois, Indiana, Kentucky, Missouri, New York, Pennsylvania., 1909; 000095
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Newfoundland., 1910; 000096
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Newfoundland, Nova Scotia., 1910; 000097
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Newfoundland., 1910; 000098
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Maryland, New Jersey, New York, Pennsylvania, West Virginia., 1910; 000099
  - Field Notebooks., 1911-1920; 001006
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Virginia, West Virginia, & Maryland., 1911; 000100
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Florida. 1911, 1912, 000101
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Ontario. 1911, 1912, 000103
    - Notebook. Field Notebook & map: Ontario., 1912; 000102
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Nova Scotia., 1912; 000104
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: New York, Pennsylvania, Ohio, Ontario., 1913; 000105
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Canada, Quebec, Nova Scotia, New Brunswick, Ontario, New York., 1913; 000106
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Nova Scotia., 1914; 000108
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: New Jersey, New York, Pennsylvania., 1914; 000109
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Pennsylvania, Virginia, & Maryland. 1914, 1915, 1916, 000110
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: California; Arizona., 1915; 000111
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Maine, Massachusetts, New Hampshire, New York, Ohio, Rhode Island, Ontario (Canada). 1916, 1917, 1920, 000112
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Newfoundland., 1918; 000113
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Newfoundland., 1918; 000114
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Oklahoma., 1919; 000115
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Quebec., 1919; 000116
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Texas, Oklahoma., 1919; 000117
  - Field Notebooks., 1921-1930; 001007
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Maryland, Washington, DC., 1921; 000118
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Massachusetts, New Hampshire, Vermont., 1921; 000119
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Oklahoma, Texas., 1922; 000120
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Vermont., 1922; 000121
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Maine, New Jersey, Vermont., 1923; 000122
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Arizona, Texas. 1923, 1924, 000123
    - Notebook. Field Notebook, and Bose, 1917 sections with Udden additions: Texas., 1924; 000124
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Quebec., 1924; 000125
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Vermont. 1924, 1925, 000126
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Nova Scotia, Quebec, Vermont. 1924, 1928, 1932, 1933, 000127
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: New Hampshire, Vermont. 1924, 1926, 1928, 000128
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Arizona, New York, Ohio, Texas. 1924, 1925, 000129
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Arizona., 1925; 000130
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Arizona., 1925; 000131
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Maine, New Hampshire., 1925; 000132
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Texas,., 1926; 000133
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: New York, Texas., 1926; 000134
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: California, Oregon, Washington, Texas, British Columbia, Canada. 1926, 1927, 000135
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Alabama, Florida, New Hampshire, New York, Vermont. 1927, 1928, 1931, 1932, 1933, 000136
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Florida. 1927, 1928, 1931, 000140
    - Notebook. Field Notebook, maps and photos: Bermuda, New Brunswick, Quebec (Gaspe), Vermont, 1929; 000137
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Quebec., 1929; 000138
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Florida, Quebec, Vermont. 1929, 1930, 000139
  - Field Notebooks., 1931-1936; 001008
    - Field notes. Notes on expedition to Newfoundland: geography; photographs; drawings; maps; measured sections, 1933; 000331
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Florida, Georgia, Maine, New York, Pennsylvania, Vermont, Washington. 1933, 1934, 1935, 1936, 000141
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Florida, Illinois, Massachusetts, Ohio, Quebec, Vermont, Wisconsin. 1933, 1934, 000142
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Florida. 1935, 1936, 000143
    - Notebook. Field Notebook: Florida, New York, Quebec. 1936, 1937, 1938, 1939, 1940, 1941, 1942, 000144
- Maps, 1904-1942; Series II
  - Arizona., 001014
    - Topographic map. Grand Canyon National Park (East Half), AZ (1: 48000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1927; 001617
    - Topographic map. Composite Map of Echo Cliffs & Kaibab Sheets, AZ (1: 250000). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 001619
  - New York., 001012
  - Newfoundland., 001009
    - Hydrographic map. Newfoundland. U.S. Hydrographic Office: Hydrographic., 001666
    - Hydrographic map. Newfoundland. U.S. Hydrographic Office: Hydrographic., 001667
    - Map. Newfoundland, west coast, Shallow Bay to Portland Cove; with a few locs plotted, 1896; 002292
  - Pennsylvania., 001011
    - Topographic map. New Bloomfield, PA 30' Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1907; 001590
  - Texas., 001013
    - Topographic map. Altuda, TX 15 Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1926; 001948
  - Vermont., 001010
    - Topographic map. Castelton, VT 15' Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1897; 001614
    - Topographic map. Milton, VT-NY 15' Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1915; 001610
    - Topographic map. Milton, VT-NY 15' Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1915; 001615
    - Topographic map. St. Albans, VT 15' Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1916; 001609
    - Topographic map. St. Albans, VT 15' Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 1916; 001616
    - Topographic map. St. Albans, VT 15-min Quad., 1916; 002304
    - Topographic map. Milton, VT 15-min Quad., 1916; 002305
    - Topographic map. Rutland, VT 15' Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 001611
    - Topographic map. Brandon, VT 15' Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 001612
    - Topographic map. Middlebury, VT 15' Quad. (1: 62500). U.S. Geological Survey: Topographic., 001613
- Photographs & Drawings, 1904-1942; Series III
  Scope and Contents
  Photographs and drawings of specimens and localities.
  - Localities. Photographs and drawings of localities., 001018
    - Photographs & Negatives. Black & white prints of USNM specimens figured in Schuchert, 1919, Stromatocystites paper; repr. #613., 000649
    - Photographs & Negatives. Black and white prints of Hackberry Grove, Iowa Black and white prints, 1933; 000585
    - Photographs & Negatives. Black and white prints and negatives of people and places in Newfoundland black and white prints and negatives, 1933; 000621
    - Photographs & Negatives. Black and white lantern slides of people and places in Newfoundland Black and white prints and negatives, 1933; 000622
    - Photographs & Negatives. Black and white glass negatives of people and places in Newfoundland black and white prints and negatives, 1933; 000623
    - Photographs & Negatives. Black and white negatives and prints of people and places in Newfoundland Black and white prints and negatives, 1933; 000624
    - Photographs & Negatives. Black and white negatives & prints of people & places, small maps; Newfoundland; including aerial photographs by Richard Light, 1933; 000626
    - Photographs. Photographs with localities: Quebec., 1938; 000145
  - Specimens. Photographs and drawings of specimens., 001017
    - Drawing. Notes and drawings on Schuchert brachiopod collection., 000243
    - Drawing. Notes and drawings on Schuchert brachiopod collection., 000244
    - Photographs & Negatives. Two 4x6 black and white prints and one line drawing of the lost holotype of Helianthaster babcocki Schuchert, YPM 14792. Letter from May Dasch explaining the lost status. ca 1915, 000550
    - Photographs & Negatives. Two 4x6 black and white prints and one 4x5 black and white negative YPM 13188, Eucladia ? beecheri. ca 1915, 000551
    - Photographs & Negatives. Black and white prints of Cambrian/Ordovician exposures from New Burlington, VT. Black and white prints. 1922-1923, 000591
    - Photographs & Negatives. Black and white negatives of Brachiopods and Graptolites from Newfoundland Black and white prints and negatives, 1933; 000625
    - Photographs & Negatives. Black and white glass prints and negatives of Brachiopods and Gastropods from Newfoundland, 1933; 000627
    - Photographs & Negatives. Black & white prints of thin sections of brachiopod shell structures. Black and White prints., 000698
    - Photographs. Photographs and descriptive labels for exhibition series on Stelleroidea, 000969
- Miscellaneous, 1904-1942; Series IV
  Miscellaneous Archives including biographical material, specimen lists and locality information.
  - Biographical Material., 001019
    - Biographical Material. Will & Testament., 1941; 000248
    - Biographical Material. Memorabilia; including tape of talk on Schuchert done presented by C.O. Dunbar, photographs, autobiography, inventory of material in Yale Univ. Archives., 2003; 000776
  - Locality Information., 001021
    - Locality information. List of locs for Gaspe, Quebec. 1900-1938, 000651
    - Locality information. Locality number conversions for Anticosti Island material: Anticosti Island, Quebec. 1908, 1909, 1919, 000001
    - Locality information. Strat. & Paleo. notes; Maine, Massachusetts. 1923-1938, 000659
    - Locality information. loc info for Devonian Gaspe Ss, 1.5 mi W of Gaspe, Quebec (links locs D9471, D9594, & D9600 as being from the same loc.), 000878
  - Miscellaneous., 001022
    - Loan form. List of trilobites from the Minnesota collection sent on loan to J. M. Clarke in 1892. (Stored in accession folder), 26 Oct 1892; 002420
    - Miscellaneous. Lecture notes on conglomerates, for Geological Club Evening [Journal Club of Yale Geol. Dept.], 1920; 000652
    - Miscellaneous. Notes on Burgess Shale fauna: British Columbia., 1921; 000197
    - Miscellaneous. Notes on Greger brachiopod collection & library., 1924; 000225
    - Miscellaneous. History of Fred Braun Collection., 1931; 000239
    - Miscellaneous. List of accession numbers and associated names; used mostly in Brachiopod coll., 000816
    - Miscellaneous. Old Schuchert loan forms, 000941
    - List of Recent Brachiopoda after Davidson (by genus). Also, notes about a synonymic and bibliographic catalogue of recent Brachiopoda., 002695
  - Specimen Lists., 001020
    - Field notes. Saudi Arabia field trip with Whitey Hagadorn; Solnhofen; (Notebook 2006-1), 000848
    - Specimen List. Catalog of bryozoa species: France., 1905; 000198
    - Specimen List. Catalog of brachiopod collection: Vermont. 1923, 1932, 000196
    - Specimen List. Catalog of specimen lots: Virginia. (does not match with any Schuchert notebooks or accessions), 000165
    - Specimen List. List of casts of U.S.N.M. brachiopods made by Preston Cloud for the Schuchert Brachiopod Collection., 000329
- Manuscript material, 1904-1942; Series V
  Manuscript material, including hand-colored maps for "Paleogeography of North America."
  - Plates. Hand-colored maps used to create the plates in "Paleogeography of North America."., 002481
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002488
    - Schuchert hand-colored map. Early Upper Cretaceous (Lower Coloradoan, Benton) = Late Turonian. Map 73., 002489
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002490
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002491
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002492
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002493
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002494
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002495
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002496
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002497
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002498
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002499
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002500
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002501
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002502
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002503
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002504
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002505
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002506
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002507
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002508
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002509
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002510
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002511
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002512
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002513
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002514
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002515
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002516
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002517
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002518
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002519
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002520
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002521
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002522
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002523
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002524
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002525
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002526
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002527
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002528
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002529
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002530
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002531
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002532
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002533
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002534
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002535
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002536
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002537
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002538
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002539
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002540
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002541
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002542
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002543
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002544
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002545
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002546
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002547
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002548
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002549
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002550
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002551
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002552
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002553
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002554
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002555
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002556
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002557
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002558
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002559
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002560
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002561
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002562
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002563
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002564
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002565
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002566
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002567
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002568
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002569
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002570
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002571
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002572
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002573
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002574
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002575
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002576
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002577
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002578
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002579
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002580
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002581
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002582
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002583
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002584
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002585
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002586
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002587
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002588
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002589
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002590
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002591
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002592
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002593
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002594
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002595
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002596
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002597
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002598
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002599
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002600
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002601
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002602
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002603
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002604
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002605
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002606
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002607
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002608
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002609
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002610
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002611
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002612
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002613
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002614
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002615
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002616
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002617
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002618
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002619
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002620
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002621
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002622
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002623
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002624
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002625
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002626
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002627
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002628
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002629
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002630
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002631
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002632
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002633
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002634
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002635
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002636
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002637
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002638
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002639
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002640
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002641
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002642
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002643
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002644
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002645
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002646
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002647
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002648
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002649
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002650
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002651
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002652
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002653
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002654
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002655
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002656
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002657
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002658
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002659
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002660
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002661
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002662
    - Schuchert hand-colored map., 002663